[
  {
    "2012 Rank": 1,
    "Question": "WHAT IS THE NAME OF THE HORSE-LIKE ANIMAL WITH BLACK AND WHITE STRIPES?",
    "Answer": "ZEBRA",
    "Correct": 0.933
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 2,
    "Question": "WHAT IS THE NAME OF THE LONG SLEEP SOME ANIMALS GO THROUGH DURING THE ENTIRE WINTER?",
    "Answer": "HIBERNATION",
    "Correct": 0.89
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 3,
    "Question": "WHAT IS THE NAME OF THE RUBBER OBJECT THAT IS HIT BACK AND FORTH BY HOCKEY PLAYERS?",
    "Answer": "PUCK",
    "Correct": 0.888
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 4,
    "Question": "WHAT IS THE NAME OF THE REMAINS OF PLANTS AND ANIMALS THAT ARE FOUND IN STONE?",
    "Answer": "FOSSILS",
    "Correct": 0.873
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 5,
    "Question": "WHICH PRECIOUS GEM IS RED?",
    "Answer": "RUBY",
    "Correct": 0.849
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 6,
    "Question": "WHAT IS THE NAME OF THE SEVERE HEADACHE THAT RETURNS PERIODICALLY AND OFTEN IS ACCOMPANIED BY NAUSEA?",
    "Answer": "MIGRAINE",
    "Correct": 0.847
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 7,
    "Question": "WHAT IS THE LAST NAME OF THE AUTHOR WHO WROTE “ROMEO AND JULIET”?",
    "Answer": "SHAKESPEARE",
    "Correct": 0.843
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 8,
    "Question": "WHAT IS THE NAME OF A DRIED GRAPE?",
    "Answer": "RAISIN",
    "Correct": 0.835
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 9,
    "Question": "WHAT IS THE NAME OF THE COMIC STRIP CHARACTER WHO EATS SPINACH TO INCREASE HIS STRENGTH?",
    "Answer": "POPEYE",
    "Correct": 0.824
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 10,
    "Question": "WHAT ANIMAL RUNS THE FASTEST?",
    "Answer": "CHEETAH",
    "Correct": 0.816
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 11,
    "Question": "WHAT IS THE NAME OF THE PROCESS BY WHICH PLANTS MAKE THEIR FOOD?",
    "Answer": "PHOTOSYNTHESIS",
    "Correct": 0.8
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 12,
    "Question": "WHAT IS THE NAME OF DOROTHY’S DOG IN “THE WIZARD OF OZ”?",
    "Answer": "TOTO",
    "Correct": 0.799
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 13,
    "Question": "WHAT IS THE NAME OF THE MOLTEN ROCK THAT RUNS DOWN THE SIDE OF A VOLCANO DURING AN ERUPTION?",
    "Answer": "LAVA",
    "Correct": 0.793
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 14,
    "Question": "WHAT WAS THE NAME OF THE SUPPOSEDLY UNSINKABLE SHIP THAT SUNK ON ITS MAIDEN VOYAGE IN 1912?",
    "Answer": "TITANIC",
    "Correct": 0.789
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 15,
    "Question": "WHICH SPORT USES THE TERMS “GUTTER” AND “ALLEY”?",
    "Answer": "BOWLING",
    "Correct": 0.788
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 16,
    "Question": "WHAT IS THE NAME OF A GIANT OCEAN WAVE CAUSED BY AN EARTHQUAKE?",
    "Answer": "TSUNAMI",
    "Correct": 0.784
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 17,
    "Question": "WHAT IS THE TERM FOR HITTING A VOLLEYBALL DOWN HARD INTO THE OPPONENT’S COURT?",
    "Answer": "SPIKE",
    "Correct": 0.784
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 18,
    "Question": "WHAT IS THE LAST NAME OF THE VILLAINOUS CAPTAIN IN THE STORY “PETER PAN”?",
    "Answer": "HOOK",
    "Correct": 0.781
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 19,
    "Question": "WHAT WAS THE NAME OF TARZAN’S GIRLFRIEND?",
    "Answer": "JANE",
    "Correct": 0.781
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 20,
    "Question": "WHAT IS THE LAST NAME OF THE BROTHERS WHO FLEW THE FIRST AIRPLANE AT KITTY HAWK?",
    "Answer": "WRIGHT",
    "Correct": 0.751
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 21,
    "Question": "WHAT IS THE NAME FOR A MEDICAL DOCTOR WHO SPECIALIZES IN CUTTING THE BODY?",
    "Answer": "SURGEON",
    "Correct": 0.748
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 22,
    "Question": "WHAT IS THE LAST NAME OF THE FIRST PERSON TO SET FOOT ON THE MOON?",
    "Answer": "ARMSTRONG",
    "Correct": 0.741
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 23,
    "Question": "WHAT IS THE CAPITAL OF FRANCE?",
    "Answer": "PARIS",
    "Correct": 0.73
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 24,
    "Question": "WHAT IS THE NAME OF THE CRIME IN WHICH A BUILDING OR PROPERTY IS PURPOSELY SET ON FIRE?",
    "Answer": "ARSON",
    "Correct": 0.722
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 25,
    "Question": "WHAT IS THE NAME OF THE SHORT PLEATED SKIRT WORN BY MEN IN SCOTLAND?",
    "Answer": "KILT",
    "Correct": 0.717
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 26,
    "Question": "WHAT IS THE NAME OF AN INABILITY TO SLEEP?",
    "Answer": "INSOMNIA",
    "Correct": 0.714
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 27,
    "Question": "WHAT IS THE NAME FOR A MEDICAL DOCTOR WHO SPECIALIZES IN DISEASES OF THE SKIN?",
    "Answer": "DERMATOLOGIST",
    "Correct": 0.692
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 28,
    "Question": "WHAT IS THE NAME OF THE LARGEST OCEAN ON EARTH?",
    "Answer": "PACIFIC",
    "Correct": 0.685
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 29,
    "Question": "WHAT IS THE NAME OF THE SHIP THAT CARRIED THE PILGRIMS TO AMERICA IN 1620?",
    "Answer": "MAYFLOWER",
    "Correct": 0.663
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 30,
    "Question": "WHAT IS THE NAME FOR A CYCLONE THAT OCCURS OVER LAND?",
    "Answer": "TORNADO",
    "Correct": 0.641
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 31,
    "Question": "WHICH SPORT IS ASSOCIATED WITH WIMBLEDON?",
    "Answer": "TENNIS",
    "Correct": 0.619
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 32,
    "Question": "WHAT IS THE NAME OF THE BIRD THAT CANNOT FLY AND IS THE LARGEST BIRD ON EARTH?",
    "Answer": "OSTRICH",
    "Correct": 0.603
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 33,
    "Question": "WHAT IS THE NAME OF THE ISLAND-CITY BELIEVED SINCE ANTIQUITY TO HAVE SUNK INTO THE OCEAN?",
    "Answer": "ATLANTIS",
    "Correct": 0.593
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 34,
    "Question": "WHAT IS THE NAME OF THE LIZARD THAT CHANGES ITS COLOR TO MATCH THE SURROUNDINGS?",
    "Answer": "CHAMELEON",
    "Correct": 0.589
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 35,
    "Question": "WHAT IS THE NAME OF THE THICK LAYER OF FAT ON A WHALE?",
    "Answer": "BLUBBER",
    "Correct": 0.572
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 36,
    "Question": "WHAT IS THE LAST NAME OF THE BASEBALL PLAYER WHO HAD THE MOST HOME RUNS IN A SINGLE SEASON PRIOR TO 1961?",
    "Answer": "RUTH",
    "Correct": 0.568
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 37,
    "Question": "WHAT IS THE NAME OF A YOUNG SHEEP?",
    "Answer": "LAMB",
    "Correct": 0.561
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 38,
    "Question": "WHAT IS THE LARGEST PLANET IN THE SOLAR SYSTEM?",
    "Answer": "JUPITER",
    "Correct": 0.559
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 39,
    "Question": "WHAT IS THE NAME OF THE NAVIGATION INSTRUMENT USED AT SEA TO PLOT POSITION RELATIVE TO THE MAGNETIC NORTH POLE?",
    "Answer": "COMPASS",
    "Correct": 0.526
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 40,
    "Question": "WHAT IS THE TERM IN GOLF REFERRING TO A SCORE OF ONE UNDER PAR ON A PARTICULAR HOLE?",
    "Answer": "BIRDIE",
    "Correct": 0.523
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 41,
    "Question": "WHICH GAME USES A RUBBER BALL AND LITTLE METAL PIECES?",
    "Answer": "JACKS",
    "Correct": 0.521
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 42,
    "Question": "WHAT IS THE NAME OF A DRIED PLUM?",
    "Answer": "PRUNE",
    "Correct": 0.517
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 43,
    "Question": "IN WHICH SPORT DOES A RIDER ON HORSEBACK HIT A BALL WITH HIS MALLET?",
    "Answer": "POLO",
    "Correct": 0.51
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 44,
    "Question": "WHAT IS THE NAME OF THE LEGENDARY ONE-EYED GIANT IN GREEK MYTHOLOGY?",
    "Answer": "CYCLOPS",
    "Correct": 0.507
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 45,
    "Question": "IN WHAT PARK IS “OLD FAITHFUL” LOCATED?",
    "Answer": "YELLOWSTONE",
    "Correct": 0.491
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 46,
    "Question": "WHAT IS THE NAME OF THE POKER HAND IN WHICH ALL OF THE CARDS ARE OF THE SAME SUIT?",
    "Answer": "FLUSH",
    "Correct": 0.486
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 47,
    "Question": "IN WHICH SPORT IS THE STANLEY CUP AWARDED?",
    "Answer": "HOCKEY",
    "Correct": 0.481
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 48,
    "Question": "WHAT IS THE NAME OF THE CHAPEL WHOSE CEILING WAS PAINTED BY MICHELANGELO?",
    "Answer": "SISTINE",
    "Correct": 0.475
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 49,
    "Question": "OF WHICH COUNTRY IS BAGHDAD THE CAPITAL?",
    "Answer": "IRAQ",
    "Correct": 0.468
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 50,
    "Question": "WHAT IS THE NAME OF THE LIQUID PORTION OF WHOLE BLOOD?",
    "Answer": "PLASMA",
    "Correct": 0.468
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 51,
    "Question": "WHAT IS THE NAME OF THE CITY IN ITALY THAT IS KNOWN FOR ITS CANALS?",
    "Answer": "VENICE",
    "Correct": 0.459
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 52,
    "Question": "WHAT IS THE NAME OF THE SPEAR LIKE OBJECT THAT IS THROWN DURING A TRACK MEET?",
    "Answer": "JAVELIN",
    "Correct": 0.452
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 53,
    "Question": "WHAT IS THE LAST NAME OF THE MAN WHO RODE HORSEBACK IN 1775 TO WARN THAT THE BRITISH WERE COMING?",
    "Answer": "REVERE",
    "Correct": 0.443
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 54,
    "Question": "WHO WAS THE EGYPTIAN QUEEN WHO JOINED FORCES WITH MARK ANTONY OF ROME?",
    "Answer": "CLEOPATRA",
    "Correct": 0.443
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 55,
    "Question": "WHAT IS THE LAST NAME OF THE MAN WHO ASSASSINATED ABRAHAM LINCOLN?",
    "Answer": "BOOTH",
    "Correct": 0.438
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 56,
    "Question": "WHAT IS THE LAST NAME OF THE MAN WHO SHOWED THAT LIGHTNING IS ELECTRIC?",
    "Answer": "FRANKLIN",
    "Correct": 0.437
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 57,
    "Question": "WHAT IS THE LAST NAME OF THE FAMOUS MAGICIAN AND ESCAPE ARTIST WHO DIED OF APPENDICITIS?",
    "Answer": "HOUDINI",
    "Correct": 0.436
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 58,
    "Question": "WHAT IS THE NAME OF DEER MEAT?",
    "Answer": "VENISON",
    "Correct": 0.432
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 59,
    "Question": "WHAT IS THE NAME OF THE LARGE HAIRY SPIDER THAT LIVES NEAR BANANAS?",
    "Answer": "TARANTULA",
    "Correct": 0.429
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 60,
    "Question": "WHAT IS THE NAME OF THE OCEAN THAT IS LOCATED BETWEEN AFRICA AND AUSTRALIA?",
    "Answer": "INDIAN",
    "Correct": 0.427
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 61,
    "Question": "WHAT IS THE LAST NAME OF THE SINGER WHO RECORDED “HEARTBREAK HOTEL” AND “ALL SHOOK UP”?",
    "Answer": "PRESLEY",
    "Correct": 0.424
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 62,
    "Question": "WHAT IS THE NAME OF THE CRIME IN WHICH A PERSON PURPOSELY BETRAYS HIS COUNTRY?",
    "Answer": "TREASON",
    "Correct": 0.418
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 63,
    "Question": "WHAT IS THE NAME OF THE FIRST ARTIFICIAL SATELLITE PUT IN ORBIT BY RUSSIA IN 1957?",
    "Answer": "SPUTNIK",
    "Correct": 0.417
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 64,
    "Question": "WHAT BRAND OF CIGARETTE WAS FIRST TO HAVE THE FLIP-TOP BOX?",
    "Answer": "MARLBORO",
    "Correct": 0.399
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 65,
    "Question": "WHAT KIND OF METAL IS ASSOCIATED WITH A 50TH WEDDING ANNIVERSARY?",
    "Answer": "GOLD",
    "Correct": 0.396
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 66,
    "Question": "WHICH TYPE OF SNAKE DO ASIAN SNAKE-CHARMERS USE?",
    "Answer": "COBRA",
    "Correct": 0.391
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 67,
    "Question": "WHAT IS THE ONLY LIQUID METAL AT ROOM TEMPERATURE?",
    "Answer": "MERCURY",
    "Correct": 0.388
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 68,
    "Question": "WHAT IS THE NAME OF THE DESERT PEOPLE WHO WANDER INSTEAD OF LIVING IN ONE PLACE?",
    "Answer": "NOMADS",
    "Correct": 0.352
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 69,
    "Question": "WHAT IS THE CAPITAL OF NEW YORK?",
    "Answer": "ALBANY",
    "Correct": 0.331
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 70,
    "Question": "WHAT IS THE NAME OF THE ORGAN THAT PRODUCES INSULIN?",
    "Answer": "PANCREAS",
    "Correct": 0.327
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 71,
    "Question": "WHAT IS THE NAME OF THE COLLAR BONE?",
    "Answer": "CLAVICLE",
    "Correct": 0.324
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 72,
    "Question": "WHAT IS THE NAME OF THE EXTINCT REPTILES KNOWN AS “TERRIBLE LIZARDS”?",
    "Answer": "DINOSAURS",
    "Correct": 0.315
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 73,
    "Question": "WHAT IS THE CAPITAL OF RUSSIA?",
    "Answer": "MOSCOW",
    "Correct": 0.309
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 74,
    "Question": "WHICH BREED OF CAT HAS BLUE EYES?",
    "Answer": "SIAMESE",
    "Correct": 0.308
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 75,
    "Question": "WHAT IS THE LAST NAME OF THE SECOND U.S. PRESIDENT?",
    "Answer": "ADAMS",
    "Correct": 0.303
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 76,
    "Question": "WHAT IS THE NAME OF THE CONSTELLATION THAT LOOKS LIKE A FLYING HORSE?",
    "Answer": "PEGASUS",
    "Correct": 0.3
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 77,
    "Question": "WHAT IS THE NAME OF THE KIND OF CAT THAT SPOKE TO ALICE IN THE STORY “ALICE’S ADVENTURES IN WONDERLAND”?",
    "Answer": "CHESHIRE",
    "Correct": 0.3
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 78,
    "Question": "WHAT IS THE LAST NAME OF THE MAN WHO PROPOSED THE THEORY OF RELATIVITY?",
    "Answer": "EINSTEIN",
    "Correct": 0.297
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 79,
    "Question": "WHAT WAS THE LAST NAME OF THE WOMAN WHO SUPPOSEDLY DESIGNED AND SEWED THE FIRST AMERICAN FLAG?",
    "Answer": "ROSS",
    "Correct": 0.286
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 80,
    "Question": "WHAT IS THE LAST NAME OF THE FIRST SIGNER OF THE “DECLARATION OF INDEPENDENCE”?",
    "Answer": "HANCOCK",
    "Correct": 0.285
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 81,
    "Question": "WHAT WAS THE NAME OF KING ARTHUR’S SWORD?",
    "Answer": "EXCALIBUR",
    "Correct": 0.285
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 82,
    "Question": "WHAT IS THE WORD THAT MEANS A NAUTICAL MILE PER HOUR?",
    "Answer": "KNOT",
    "Correct": 0.277
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 83,
    "Question": "WHAT IS THE NAME FOR THE ASTRONOMICAL BODIES THAT ENTER THE EARTH’S ATMOSPHERE?",
    "Answer": "METEORS",
    "Correct": 0.271
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 84,
    "Question": "WHAT IS THE LONGEST RIVER IN SOUTH AMERICA?",
    "Answer": "AMAZON",
    "Correct": 0.267
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 85,
    "Question": "WHAT IS THE NAME OF THE AUTOMOBILE INSTRUMENT THAT MEASURES MILEAGE?",
    "Answer": "ODOMETER",
    "Correct": 0.258
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 86,
    "Question": "WHAT ITALIAN CITY WAS DESTROYED WHEN MOUNT VESUVIUS ERUPTED IN 79 A.D.?",
    "Answer": "POMPEII",
    "Correct": 0.258
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 87,
    "Question": "WHAT IS THE LAST NAME OF BATMAN’S SECRET IDENTITY IN THE BATMAN COMICS?",
    "Answer": "WAYNE",
    "Correct": 0.252
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 88,
    "Question": "WHAT IS THE LAST NAME OF THE MYTHICAL GIANT LUMBERJACK?",
    "Answer": "BUNYAN",
    "Correct": 0.245
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 89,
    "Question": "WHAT IS THE NAME OF THE COMPANY THAT PRODUCES “BABY RUTH” CANDY BARS?",
    "Answer": "NESTLE",
    "Correct": 0.245
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 90,
    "Question": "WHAT IS THE NAME OF SOCRATES’ MOST FAMOUS STUDENT?",
    "Answer": "PLATO",
    "Correct": 0.239
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 91,
    "Question": "WHAT IS THE NAME OF THE THREE-LEAF CLOVER THAT IS THE EMBLEM OF IRELAND?",
    "Answer": "SHAMROCK",
    "Correct": 0.239
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 92,
    "Question": "OF WHICH COUNTRY IS BUENOS AIRES THE CAPITAL?",
    "Answer": "ARGENTINA",
    "Correct": 0.204
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 93,
    "Question": "WHAT IS THE LAST NAME OF THE ACTRESS WHO RECEIVED THE BEST ACTRESS AWARD FOR THE MOVIE “MARY POPPINS”?",
    "Answer": "ANDREWS",
    "Correct": 0.203
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 94,
    "Question": "WHAT IS THE NAME OF THE MOUNTAIN RANGE IN WHICH MOUNT EVEREST IS LOCATED?",
    "Answer": "HIMALAYAS",
    "Correct": 0.198
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 95,
    "Question": "WHAT IS THE UNIT OF SOUND INTENSITY?",
    "Answer": "DECIBEL",
    "Correct": 0.19
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 96,
    "Question": "WHAT IS THE NAME OF THE PROJECT WHICH DEVELOPED THE ATOMIC BOMB DURING WORLD WAR II?",
    "Answer": "MANHATTAN",
    "Correct": 0.188
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 97,
    "Question": "WHAT IS THE UNIT OF ELECTRICAL POWER THAT REFERS TO A CURRENT OF ONE AMPERE AT ONE VOLT?",
    "Answer": "WATT",
    "Correct": 0.187
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 98,
    "Question": "WHAT IS THE LAST NAME OF THE AUTHOR OF THE BOOK “1984”?",
    "Answer": "ORWELL",
    "Correct": 0.185
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 99,
    "Question": "IN WHICH GAME ARE MEN CROWNED?",
    "Answer": "CHECKERS",
    "Correct": 0.176
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 100,
    "Question": "WHAT IS THE LAST NAME OF THE MAN WHO ASSASSINATED PRESIDENT JOHN F. KENNEDY?",
    "Answer": "OSWALD",
    "Correct": 0.172
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 101,
    "Question": "WHAT IS THE NAME OF BATMAN’S BUTLER?",
    "Answer": "ALFRED",
    "Correct": 0.163
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 102,
    "Question": "WHICH COUNTRY WAS THE FIRST TO USE GUNPOWDER?",
    "Answer": "CHINA",
    "Correct": 0.16
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 103,
    "Question": "WHAT IS THE NAME OF AN AIRPLANE WITHOUT AN ENGINE?",
    "Answer": "GLIDER",
    "Correct": 0.157
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 104,
    "Question": "WHAT IS THE NAME OF THE NORTH STAR?",
    "Answer": "POLARIS",
    "Correct": 0.156
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 105,
    "Question": "WHAT IS THE ONLY WORD THAT THE RAVEN SAYS IN EDGAR ALLEN POE’S POEM “THE RAVEN”?",
    "Answer": "NEVERMORE",
    "Correct": 0.155
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 106,
    "Question": "FOR WHICH COUNTRY IS THE YEN THE MONETARY UNIT?",
    "Answer": "JAPAN",
    "Correct": 0.152
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 107,
    "Question": "IN WHAT EUROPEAN CITY IS THE PARTHENON LOCATED?",
    "Answer": "ATHENS",
    "Correct": 0.15
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 108,
    "Question": "WHAT IS THE NAME OF THE FURRY ANIMAL THAT ATTACKS COBRA SNAKES?",
    "Answer": "MONGOOSE",
    "Correct": 0.149
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 109,
    "Question": "FOR WHICH COUNTRY IS THE RUPEE THE MONETARY UNIT?",
    "Answer": "INDIA",
    "Correct": 0.147
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 110,
    "Question": "WHAT IS THE LAST NAME OF THE MAN WHO FIRST STUDIED GENETIC INHERITANCE IN PLANTS?",
    "Answer": "MENDEL",
    "Correct": 0.144
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 111,
    "Question": "WHAT IS THE LAST NAME OF THE MAN WHO WROTE THE “STAR SPANGLED BANNER”?",
    "Answer": "KEY",
    "Correct": 0.141
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 112,
    "Question": "WHAT IS THE NAME OF THE PALACE IN LONDON IN WHICH THE MONARCH OF ENGLAND RESIDES?",
    "Answer": "BUCKINGHAM",
    "Correct": 0.141
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 113,
    "Question": "IN WHICH GAME ARE THE STANDARD PIECES OF STAUNTON DESIGN?",
    "Answer": "CHESS",
    "Correct": 0.138
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 114,
    "Question": "WHAT ARE PEOPLE WHO MAKE MAPS CALLED?",
    "Answer": "CARTOGRAPHERS",
    "Correct": 0.138
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 115,
    "Question": "WHAT WAS THE NAME OF THE ZEPPELIN THAT EXPLODED IN LAKEHURST N.J. IN 1937?",
    "Answer": "HINDENBURG",
    "Correct": 0.134
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 116,
    "Question": "WHAT IS THE PALACE BUILT IN FRANCE BY KING LOUIS XIV?",
    "Answer": "VERSAILLES",
    "Correct": 0.128
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 117,
    "Question": "IN WHICH CITY IS THE U.S. NAVAL ACADEMY LOCATED?",
    "Answer": "ANNAPOLIS",
    "Correct": 0.127
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 118,
    "Question": "WHAT IS THE NAME OF THE LIGHTEST WOOD KNOWN?",
    "Answer": "BALSA",
    "Correct": 0.125
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 119,
    "Question": "WHAT IS THE LAST NAME OF THE BOXER WHO LATER BECAME KNOWN AS MUHAMMAD ALI?",
    "Answer": "CLAY",
    "Correct": 0.117
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 120,
    "Question": "WHAT ISLAND IS THE LARGEST IN THE WORLD EXCLUDING AUSTRALIA?",
    "Answer": "GREENLAND",
    "Correct": 0.111
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 121,
    "Question": "WHAT IS THE NAME OF THE SMALL JAPANESE STOVE USED FOR OUTDOOR COOKING?",
    "Answer": "HIBACHI",
    "Correct": 0.11
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 122,
    "Question": "WHAT IS THE LAST NAME OF THE WOMAN WHO BEGAN THE PROFESSION OF NURSING?",
    "Answer": "NIGHTINGALE",
    "Correct": 0.108
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 123,
    "Question": "WHO WAS THE LEADER OF THE ARGONAUTS?",
    "Answer": "JASON",
    "Correct": 0.107
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 124,
    "Question": "WHAT IS THE LAST NAME OF THE ARTIST WHO PAINTED “GUERNICA”?",
    "Answer": "PICASSO",
    "Correct": 0.107
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 125,
    "Question": "IN WHAT ANCIENT CITY WERE THE “HANGING GARDENS” LOCATED?",
    "Answer": "BABYLON",
    "Correct": 0.103
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 126,
    "Question": "WHAT ARE PEOPLE CALLED WHO EXPLORE CAVES?",
    "Answer": "SPELUNKERS",
    "Correct": 0.1
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 127,
    "Question": "WHAT IS THE NAME OF THE CAPTAIN OF THE PEQUOD IN THE BOOK “MOBY DICK”?",
    "Answer": "AHAB",
    "Correct": 0.097
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 128,
    "Question": "WHAT IS THE CAPITAL OF KENTUCKY?",
    "Answer": "FRANKFORT",
    "Correct": 0.095
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 129,
    "Question": "WHAT IS THE NAME OF AN ILLEGAL MOVE BY A BASEBALL PITCHER THAT RESULTS IN ALL RUNNERS ADVANCING ONE BASE?",
    "Answer": "BALK",
    "Correct": 0.093
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 130,
    "Question": "WHAT IS THE LAST NAME OF THE AMERICAN WHO STARRED IN THE 1936 OLYMPICS?",
    "Answer": "OWENS",
    "Correct": 0.093
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 131,
    "Question": "THE DEEPEST PART OF THE OCEAN IS LOCATED AT WHICH TRENCH?",
    "Answer": "MARIANA",
    "Correct": 0.093
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 132,
    "Question": "WHICH SPORT USES THE TERMS “STONES” AND “BROOMS”?",
    "Answer": "CURLING",
    "Correct": 0.092
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 133,
    "Question": "WHAT IS THE PROPER NAME FOR A BADMINTON BIRD?",
    "Answer": "SHUTTLECOCK",
    "Correct": 0.091
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 134,
    "Question": "WHAT IS THE LAST NAME OF THE AUTHOR WHO WROTE “OLIVER TWIST”?",
    "Answer": "DICKENS",
    "Correct": 0.09
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 135,
    "Question": "WHAT IS THE CAPITAL OF DELAWARE?",
    "Answer": "DOVER",
    "Correct": 0.09
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 136,
    "Question": "WHAT IS THE LAST NAME OF THE MAN WHO INVENTED THE PHONOGRAPH?",
    "Answer": "EDISON",
    "Correct": 0.086
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 137,
    "Question": "IN WHICH TYPE OF SKI RACE DOES THE DOWNHILL SKIER MAKE SHARP TURNS AROUND POLES?",
    "Answer": "SLALOM",
    "Correct": 0.086
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 138,
    "Question": "IN WHICH CITY IS HEATHROW AIRPORT LOCATED?",
    "Answer": "LONDON",
    "Correct": 0.083
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 139,
    "Question": "WHAT IS THE CAPITAL OF JAMAICA?",
    "Answer": "KINGSTON",
    "Correct": 0.081
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 140,
    "Question": "WHICH PLANET WAS THE LAST TO BE DISCOVERED?",
    "Answer": "NEPTUNE",
    "Correct": 0.08
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 141,
    "Question": "WHAT IS THE LAST NAME OF THE AUTHOR WHO WROTE “THE MURDERS IN THE RUE MORGUE”?",
    "Answer": "POE",
    "Correct": 0.08
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 142,
    "Question": "WHAT IS THE NAME OF THE SHIP ON WHICH CHARLES DARWIN MADE HIS SCIENTIFIC VOYAGE?",
    "Answer": "BEAGLE",
    "Correct": 0.079
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 143,
    "Question": "WHAT IS THE CAPITAL OF CHILE?",
    "Answer": "SANTIAGO",
    "Correct": 0.077
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 144,
    "Question": "WHAT IS THE LAST NAME OF THE AUTHOR WHO WROTE “THE OLD MAN AND THE SEA”?",
    "Answer": "HEMINGWAY",
    "Correct": 0.077
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 145,
    "Question": "WHAT IS THE LAST NAME OF THE MAN WHO WROTE “CANTERBURY TALES”?",
    "Answer": "CHAUCER",
    "Correct": 0.076
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 146,
    "Question": "WHAT IS THE NAME OF THE FOUNTAIN IN ROME INTO WHICH COINS ARE THROWN FOR GOOD LUCK?",
    "Answer": "TREVI",
    "Correct": 0.071
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 147,
    "Question": "WHAT WAS THE LAST NAME OF THE MAN WHO WAS PRESIDENT DIRECTLY AFTER JAMES MADISON?",
    "Answer": "MONROE",
    "Correct": 0.068
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 148,
    "Question": "WHAT IS THE LAST NAME OF THE ASTRONOMER WHO PUBLISHED IN 1543 HIS THEORY THAT THE EARTH REVOLVES AROUND THE SUN?",
    "Answer": "COPERNICUS",
    "Correct": 0.067
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 149,
    "Question": "WHAT IS THE LAST NAME OF THE CRIMINAL WHO WAS KNOWN AS “SCARFACE”?",
    "Answer": "CAPONE",
    "Correct": 0.066
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 150,
    "Question": "WHAT IS THE NAME OF THE LONE RANGER’S INDIAN SIDEKICK?",
    "Answer": "TONTO",
    "Correct": 0.061
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 151,
    "Question": "WHAT IS THE CAPITAL OF DENMARK?",
    "Answer": "COPENHAGEN",
    "Correct": 0.06
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 152,
    "Question": "WHAT WAS THE LAST NAME OF THE MAN WHO WAS THE RADIO BROADCASTER FOR THE “WAR OF THE WORLDS”?",
    "Answer": "WELLES",
    "Correct": 0.059
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 153,
    "Question": "IN WHICH CITY IS MICHELANGELO’S STATUE OF DAVID LOCATED?",
    "Answer": "FLORENCE",
    "Correct": 0.058
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 154,
    "Question": "WHAT WAS FRANK LLOYD WRIGHT’S PROFESSION?",
    "Answer": "ARCHITECT",
    "Correct": 0.058
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 155,
    "Question": "OF WHICH COUNTRY IS NAIROBI THE CAPITAL?",
    "Answer": "KENYA",
    "Correct": 0.053
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 156,
    "Question": "WHAT IS THE NAME OF THE HILLBILLY FAMILY THAT HAD A FAMOUS FEUD WITH THE MCCOY FAMILY?",
    "Answer": "HATFIELD",
    "Correct": 0.052
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 157,
    "Question": "WHAT KIND OF POISON DID SOCRATES TAKE AS HIS EXECUTION?",
    "Answer": "HEMLOCK",
    "Correct": 0.052
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 158,
    "Question": "WHAT IS THE LAST NAME OF THE FIRST PERSON TO COMPLETE A SOLO FLIGHT ACROSS THE ATLANTIC OCEAN?",
    "Answer": "LINDBERGH",
    "Correct": 0.052
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 159,
    "Question": "ANDY GRIFFITH WAS THE SHERIFF OF WHAT TOWN ON TELEVISION’S “ANDY GRIFFITH SHOW”?",
    "Answer": "MAYBERRY",
    "Correct": 0.052
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 160,
    "Question": "WHAT IS THE NAME OF THE ROMAN EMPEROR WHO FIDDLED WHILE ROME BURNED?",
    "Answer": "NERO",
    "Correct": 0.052
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 161,
    "Question": "WHAT IS THE CITY IN WHICH THE BASEBALL HALL OF FAME IS LOCATED?",
    "Answer": "COOPERSTOWN",
    "Correct": 0.051
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 162,
    "Question": "WHAT IS THE NAME OF THE UNIT OF MEASURE THAT REFERS TO A SIX-FOOT DEPTH OF WATER?",
    "Answer": "FATHOM",
    "Correct": 0.051
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 163,
    "Question": "WHAT IS THE LAST NAME OF THE SCIENTIST WHO DISCOVERED RADIUM?",
    "Answer": "CURIE",
    "Correct": 0.046
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 164,
    "Question": "WHAT IS THE LAST NAME OF THE AUTHOR WHO WROTE “BRAVE NEW WORLD”?",
    "Answer": "HUXLEY",
    "Correct": 0.045
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 165,
    "Question": "IN ADDITION TO THE KENTUCKY DERBY AND THE BELMONT STAKES WHAT HORSE RACE COMPRISES THE TRIPLE CROWN?",
    "Answer": "PREAKNESS",
    "Correct": 0.044
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 166,
    "Question": "WHAT IS THE LAST NAME OF THE CRIMINAL WHO WAS KILLED BY FBI AGENTS OUTSIDE OF A CHICAGO MOVIE THEATER?",
    "Answer": "DILLINGER",
    "Correct": 0.044
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 167,
    "Question": "WHAT IS THE NAME OF THE SINGER WHO POPULARIZED A DANCE KNOWN AS THE “TWIST”?",
    "Answer": "CHECKER",
    "Correct": 0.041
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 168,
    "Question": "OVER WHICH RIVER IS THE GEORGE WASHINGTON BRIDGE?",
    "Answer": "HUDSON",
    "Correct": 0.041
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 169,
    "Question": "WHAT IS THE LAST NAME OF THE MAN WHO INVENTED DYNAMITE?",
    "Answer": "NOBEL",
    "Correct": 0.04
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 170,
    "Question": "WHAT IS THE NAME OF THE CHINESE RELIGION FOUNDED BY LAO TSE?",
    "Answer": "TAOISM",
    "Correct": 0.04
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 171,
    "Question": "WHAT IS THE LAST NAME OF THE COMMANDER WHO LOST THE BATTLE OF THE LITTLE BIGHORN RIVER?",
    "Answer": "CUSTER",
    "Correct": 0.038
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 172,
    "Question": "WHAT IS THE NAME OF THE NAVIGATION INSTRUMENT USED AT SEA TO PLOT POSITION BY THE STARS?",
    "Answer": "SEXTANT",
    "Correct": 0.038
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 173,
    "Question": "WHO WAS THE MOST FAMOUS GREEK DOCTOR?",
    "Answer": "HIPPOCRATES",
    "Correct": 0.037
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 174,
    "Question": "IN WHICH CITY DOES THE COTTON BOWL TAKE PLACE?",
    "Answer": "DALLAS",
    "Correct": 0.037
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 175,
    "Question": "WHAT IS THE LAST NAME OF THE AUTHOR WHO WROTE THE SHERLOCK HOLMES STORIES?",
    "Answer": "DOYLE",
    "Correct": 0.036
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 176,
    "Question": "FOR WHICH COUNTRY IS THE DRACHMA THE MONETARY UNIT?",
    "Answer": "GREECE",
    "Correct": 0.036
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 177,
    "Question": "WHAT IS THE NAME OF THE MANSION IN VIRGINIA THAT WAS THOMAS JEFFERSON’S HOME?",
    "Answer": "MONTICELLO",
    "Correct": 0.035
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 178,
    "Question": "WHAT IS THE LONGEST RIVER IN ASIA?",
    "Answer": "YANGTZE",
    "Correct": 0.035
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 179,
    "Question": "WHAT IS THE LAST NAME OF THE ACTOR WHO RECEIVED THE BEST ACTOR AWARD FOR THE MOVIE “ON THE WATERFRONT”?",
    "Answer": "BRANDO",
    "Correct": 0.034
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 180,
    "Question": "WHAT IS THE LAST NAME OF THE MALE STAR OF THE MOVIE “CASABLANCA”?",
    "Answer": "BOGART",
    "Correct": 0.034
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 181,
    "Question": "OF WHICH COUNTRY IS BUDAPEST THE CAPITAL?",
    "Answer": "HUNGARY",
    "Correct": 0.033
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 182,
    "Question": "WHO IS KNOWN AS “THE FATHER OF GEOMETRY”?",
    "Answer": "EUCLID",
    "Correct": 0.033
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 183,
    "Question": "WHAT IS THE LAST NAME OF THE HUSBAND-WIFE SPIES WHO WERE ELECTROCUTED IN 1951 FOR PASSING ATOMIC SECRETS TO RUSSIA?",
    "Answer": "ROSENBERG",
    "Correct": 0.031
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 184,
    "Question": "WHAT IS THE LAST NAME OF THE COMPOSER WHO WROTE THE OPERA “DON GIOVANNI”?",
    "Answer": "MOZART",
    "Correct": 0.03
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 185,
    "Question": "WHAT IS THE LAST NAME OF THE AUTHOR OF THE JAMES BOND NOVELS?",
    "Answer": "FLEMING",
    "Correct": 0.03
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 186,
    "Question": "WHAT WAS THE LAST NAME OF BUFFALO BILL?",
    "Answer": "CODY",
    "Correct": 0.03
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 187,
    "Question": "WHAT IS THE LAST NAME OF THE AUTHOR WHO WROTE UNDER THE PSEUDONYM OF MARK TWAIN?",
    "Answer": "CLEMENS",
    "Correct": 0.029
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 188,
    "Question": "WHAT IS THE NAME OF THE ISLAND ON WHICH NAPOLEON WAS BORN?",
    "Answer": "CORSICA",
    "Correct": 0.029
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 189,
    "Question": "WHAT IS THE LAST NAME OF THE DOCTOR WHO FIRST DEVELOPED A VACCINE AGAINST POLIO?",
    "Answer": "SALK",
    "Correct": 0.028
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 190,
    "Question": "WHAT IS THE LAST NAME OF THE MAN WHO BEGAN THE REFORMATION IN GERMANY?",
    "Answer": "LUTHER",
    "Correct": 0.028
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 191,
    "Question": "WHAT IS THE CAPITAL OF FINLAND?",
    "Answer": "HELSINKI",
    "Correct": 0.026
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 192,
    "Question": "WHAT WAS THE NAME OF THE APOLLO LUNAR MODULE THAT LANDED THE FIRST MAN ON THE MOON?",
    "Answer": "EAGLE",
    "Correct": 0.025
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 193,
    "Question": "WHAT IS THE LAST NAME OF THE COSMONAUT WHO WAS THE FIRST PERSON TO ORBIT AROUND THE EARTH?",
    "Answer": "GAGARIN",
    "Correct": 0.024
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 194,
    "Question": "WHAT WAS THE NAME OF ROY ROGER’S DOG?",
    "Answer": "BULLET",
    "Correct": 0.021
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 195,
    "Question": "WHAT WAS THE NAME OF ALEXANDER GRAHAM BELL’S ASSISTANT?",
    "Answer": "WATSON",
    "Correct": 0.021
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 196,
    "Question": "WHAT WAS THE LAST NAME OF THE COMPOSER OF THE “MAPLE LEAF RAG”?",
    "Answer": "JOPLIN",
    "Correct": 0.02
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 197,
    "Question": "WHAT IS THE LAST NAME OF THE PLAYWRIGHT WHO WROTE “A STREETCAR NAMED DESIRE”?",
    "Answer": "WILLIAMS",
    "Correct": 0.02
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 198,
    "Question": "WHAT IS THE LAST NAME OF THE AUTHOR OF “LITTLE WOMEN”?",
    "Answer": "ALCOTT",
    "Correct": 0.02
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 199,
    "Question": "WHAT IS THE LAST NAME OF THE FIRST PERSON TO CLIMB MOUNT EVEREST?",
    "Answer": "HILLARY",
    "Correct": 0.02
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 200,
    "Question": "WHAT IS THE LAST NAME OF THE ACTOR WHO PLAYED RHETT BUTLER IN “GONE WITH THE WIND”?",
    "Answer": "GABLE",
    "Correct": 0.02
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 201,
    "Question": "IN WHICH COUNTRY IS ANGEL FALLS LOCATED?",
    "Answer": "VENEZUELA",
    "Correct": 0.02
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 202,
    "Question": "WHAT IS THE CAPITAL OF CANADA?",
    "Answer": "OTTAWA",
    "Correct": 0.019
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 203,
    "Question": "WHAT IS THE LAST NAME OF THE TWENTY-FIRST U.S. PRESIDENT?",
    "Answer": "ARTHUR",
    "Correct": 0.019
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 204,
    "Question": "WHAT WAS THE NAME OF THE GOLDFISH IN THE STORY OF PINOCCHIO?",
    "Answer": "CLEO",
    "Correct": 0.019
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 205,
    "Question": "WHAT IS THE NAME OF THE VILLAINOUS PEOPLE WHO LIVED UNDERGROUND IN H. G. WELLS’S BOOK “THE TIME MACHINE”?",
    "Answer": "MORLOCKS",
    "Correct": 0.018
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 206,
    "Question": "WHAT WAS THE LAST NAME OF THE CHARACTER PORTRAYED BY ROBERT STACK ON THE TELEVISION SHOW “THE UNTOUCHABLES”?",
    "Answer": "NESS",
    "Correct": 0.015
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 207,
    "Question": "WHAT IS THE CAPITAL OF AUSTRALIA?",
    "Answer": "CANBERRA",
    "Correct": 0.015
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 208,
    "Question": "WHAT IS THE LAST NAME OF THE ARTIST WHO PAINTED “THE PERSISTENCE OF MEMORY”?",
    "Answer": "DALI",
    "Correct": 0.015
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 209,
    "Question": "WHAT IS THE LAST NAME OF THE MAN WHO INVENTED THE TELEGRAPH?",
    "Answer": "MORSE",
    "Correct": 0.014
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 210,
    "Question": "WHAT IS THE NAME OF THE RIVER ON WHICH BONN IS LOCATED?",
    "Answer": "RHINE",
    "Correct": 0.014
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 211,
    "Question": "WHAT IS THE NAME OF THE SUBSTANCE DERIVED FROM A WHALE THAT IS USED TO MAKE PERFUME?",
    "Answer": "AMBERGRIS",
    "Correct": 0.014
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": "212\tWHAT IS THE NAME OF THE SUBMARINE IN JULES VERNE’S “20,000 LEAGUES BENEATH THE SEA”?\tNAUTILUS\t0.014",
    "Question": "",
    "Answer": "",
    "Correct": ""
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 213,
    "Question": "WHAT WAS THE NAME OF THE CLOWN ON THE “HOWDY DOODY” TELEVISION SHOW?",
    "Answer": "CLARABELL",
    "Correct": 0.014
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 214,
    "Question": "WHAT IS THE LAST NAME OF DAGWOOD’S BOSS IN THE COMIC STRIP “BLONDIE”?",
    "Answer": "DITHERS",
    "Correct": 0.01
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 215,
    "Question": "WHAT IS THE LAST NAME OF THE MOVIE ACTOR WHO PORTRAYED SPARTACUS?",
    "Answer": "DOUGLAS",
    "Correct": 0.01
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 216,
    "Question": "WHAT IS THE LAST NAME OF THE WOMAN WHO FOUNDED THE AMERICAN RED CROSS?",
    "Answer": "BARTON",
    "Correct": 0.01
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 217,
    "Question": "WHAT IS THE LAST NAME OF THE UNION GENERAL WHO DEFEATED THE CONFEDERATE ARMY AT THE CIVIL WAR BATTLE OF GETTYSBURG?",
    "Answer": "MEADE",
    "Correct": 0.01
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 218,
    "Question": "WHAT IS THE NAME OF THE AVENUE THAT IMMEDIATELY FOLLOWS ATLANTIC AVENUE IN THE GAME OF MONOPOLY?",
    "Answer": "VENTNOR",
    "Correct": 0.01
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 219,
    "Question": "WHICH GAME USES A DOUBLING CUBE?",
    "Answer": "BACKGAMMON",
    "Correct": 0.01
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 220,
    "Question": "WHAT IS THE LAST NAME OF THE MAN WHO SUPPOSEDLY KILLED JESSE JAMES?",
    "Answer": "FORD",
    "Correct": 0.009
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 221,
    "Question": "WHAT IS THE LAST NAME OF THE EUROPEAN AUTHOR WHO WROTE “THE TRIAL”?",
    "Answer": "KAFKA",
    "Correct": 0.008
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 222,
    "Question": "THE GENERAL NAMED HANNIBAL WAS FROM WHAT CITY?",
    "Answer": "CARTHAGE",
    "Correct": 0.007
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 223,
    "Question": "WHAT IS THE LAST NAME OF THE BRITISH ADMIRAL WHO WON THE BATTLE OF TRAFALGAR?",
    "Answer": "NELSON",
    "Correct": 0.007
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 224,
    "Question": "WHAT IS THE NAME OF THE INDIAN COLLEGE IN PENNSYLVANIA FOR WHICH JIM THORPE PLAYED FOOTBALL?",
    "Answer": "CARLISLE",
    "Correct": 0.007
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 225,
    "Question": "WHAT IS THE NAME OF THE PLAY IN WHICH ELWOOD P. DOWD IS A CHARACTER?",
    "Answer": "HARVEY",
    "Correct": 0.007
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 226,
    "Question": "WHAT FAMOUS KNOT DID ALEXANDER THE GREAT UNDO?",
    "Answer": "GORDIAN",
    "Correct": 0.007
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 227,
    "Question": "WHAT WAS THE NAME OF THE UNSUCCESSFUL AUTO THAT WAS MANUFACTURED BY THE FORD MOTOR COMPANY FROM 1957–1959?",
    "Answer": "EDSEL",
    "Correct": 0.007
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 228,
    "Question": "WHAT IS THE LAST NAME OF THE SONG WRITER WHO WROTE THE SONG “I LOVE PARIS”?",
    "Answer": "PORTER",
    "Correct": 0.007
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 229,
    "Question": "WHAT IS THE LAST NAME OF THE FIRST AMERICAN AUTHOR TO WIN THE NOBEL PRIZE FOR LITERATURE?",
    "Answer": "LEWIS",
    "Correct": 0.007
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 230,
    "Question": "WHAT IS THE LAST NAME OF THE INVENTOR OF THE WIRELESS RADIO?",
    "Answer": "MARCONI",
    "Correct": 0.007
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 231,
    "Question": "WHAT IS THE LAST NAME OF THE ARTIST WHO PAINTED “AMERICAN GOTHIC”?",
    "Answer": "WOOD",
    "Correct": 0.007
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 232,
    "Question": "IN WHAT PROFESSION WAS EMMETT KELLY?",
    "Answer": "CLOWN",
    "Correct": 0.006
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 233,
    "Question": "WHAT IS THE NAME OF THE RIVER THAT RUNS THROUGH ROME?",
    "Answer": "TIBER",
    "Correct": 0.006
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 234,
    "Question": "WHAT IS THE LAST NAME OF THE POET WHO ORIGINALLY WROTE “DON JUAN”?",
    "Answer": "BYRON",
    "Correct": 0.006
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 235,
    "Question": "WHAT IS THE LAST NAME OF THE FRENCH AUTHOR WHO WROTE “THE STRANGER”?",
    "Answer": "CAMUS",
    "Correct": 0.005
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 236,
    "Question": "WHO WAS THE FIRST RULER OF THE HOLY ROMAN EMPIRE?",
    "Answer": "CHARLEMAGNE",
    "Correct": 0.005
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 237,
    "Question": "WHAT IS THE LAST NAME OF THE MAN WHO IS REGARDED AS THE NATIONAL POET OF SCOTLAND?",
    "Answer": "BURNS",
    "Correct": 0.005
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 238,
    "Question": "WHAT IS THE LAST NAME OF THE FOOTBALL PLAYER KNOWN AS “THE GALLOPING GHOST”?",
    "Answer": "GRANGE",
    "Correct": 0.005
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 239,
    "Question": "WHAT IS THE NAME OF ROY ROGERS’ HORSE?",
    "Answer": "TRIGGER",
    "Correct": 0.005
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 240,
    "Question": "WHAT WAS THE NAME OF THE NUCLEAR SUBMARINE THAT SUNK IN THE ATLANTIC IN 1963?",
    "Answer": "THRESHER",
    "Correct": 0.005
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 241,
    "Question": "WHAT IS THE NAME OF THE MAN WHO REMOVED THE THORN FROM THE LION’S PAW IN THE STORY FROM AESOP’S FABLES?",
    "Answer": "ANDROCLES",
    "Correct": 0.005
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 242,
    "Question": "WHAT IS THE NAME OF THE BRIGHTEST STAR IN THE SKY EXCLUDING THE SUN?",
    "Answer": "SIRIUS",
    "Correct": 0.005
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 243,
    "Question": "WHAT IS THE NAME OF THE LAND OF THE GIANTS IN “GULLIVER’S TRAVELS”?",
    "Answer": "BROBDINGNAG",
    "Correct": 0.005
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 244,
    "Question": "WHAT WAS THE LAST NAME OF THE FEMALE STAR OF THE MOVIE “CASABLANCA”?",
    "Answer": "BERGMAN",
    "Correct": 0.005
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 245,
    "Question": "WHAT IS THE LAST NAME OF THE ACTOR KNOWN AS “THE MAN OF A THOUSAND FACES”?",
    "Answer": "CHANEY",
    "Correct": 0.005
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 246,
    "Question": "WHAT IS THE NAME OF THE BASEBALL PLAYER WITH THE HIGHEST LIFETIME BATTING AVERAGE IN THE MAJOR LEAGUES?",
    "Answer": "COBB",
    "Correct": 0.005
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 247,
    "Question": "WHAT WAS THE LAST NAME OF THE ACTOR IN THE ROLE OF PERRY MASON ON TELEVISION?",
    "Answer": "BURR",
    "Correct": 0.005
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 248,
    "Question": "WHAT IS THE LAST NAME OF THE MOST POPULAR PIN-UP GIRL OF WORLD WAR II?",
    "Answer": "GRABLE",
    "Correct": 0.004
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 249,
    "Question": "WHAT IS THE NAME OF THE LARGEST DESERT ON EARTH?",
    "Answer": "ANTARCTICA",
    "Correct": 0
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 250,
    "Question": "WHAT IS THE LAST NAME OF THE JOCKEY WITH THE MOST LIFETIME WINNERS IN HORSE RACING?",
    "Answer": "BAZE",
    "Correct": 0
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 251,
    "Question": "WHAT IS THE LAST NAME OF THE MAN WHO WAS THE VOICE OF MR. MAGOO?",
    "Answer": "BACKUS",
    "Correct": 0
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 252,
    "Question": "WHAT IS THE LAST NAME OF THE ACTOR WHO PORTRAYED SERGEANT FRIDAY ON “DRAGNET”?",
    "Answer": "WEBB",
    "Correct": 0
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 253,
    "Question": "WHAT WAS THE LAST NAME OF THE ACTOR WHO PORTRAYED THE FATHER ON THE TELEVISION SHOW “FATHER KNOWS BEST”?",
    "Answer": "YOUNG",
    "Correct": 0
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 254,
    "Question": "WHAT WAS THE LAST NAME OF THE VENTRILOQUIST WHO PROVIDED THE VOICE FOR CHARLIE MCCARTHY?",
    "Answer": "BERGEN",
    "Correct": 0
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 255,
    "Question": "WHAT WAS THE LAST NAME OF THE CAPTAIN OF THE BRITISH SHIP “BOUNTY” WHEN THE MUTINY OCCURRED?",
    "Answer": "BLIGH",
    "Correct": 0
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 256,
    "Question": "WHAT IS THE LAST NAME OF THE INVENTOR OF THE STEAMBOAT “CLERMONT”?",
    "Answer": "FULTON",
    "Correct": 0
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 257,
    "Question": "WHAT IS THE NAME OF GERMANY’S LARGEST BATTLESHIP THAT WAS SUNK IN WORLD WAR II?",
    "Answer": "BISMARCK",
    "Correct": 0
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 258,
    "Question": "WHAT IS THE LAST NAME OF THE JUDGE WHO WAS KNOWN AS “THE LAW WEST OF THE PECOS”?",
    "Answer": "BEAN",
    "Correct": 0
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 259,
    "Question": "WHAT IS JOHN KENNETH GALBRAITH’S PROFESSION?",
    "Answer": "ECONOMIST",
    "Correct": 0
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 260,
    "Question": "WHAT WAS THE NAME OF THE UNION IRONCLAD SHIP THAT FOUGHT THE CONFEDERATE IRONCLAD MERRIMACK?",
    "Answer": "MONITOR",
    "Correct": 0
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 261,
    "Question": "WHAT IS THE LAST NAME OF THE DOCTOR WHO PERFORMED THE FIRST SUCCESSFUL HUMAN HEART TRANSPLANT?",
    "Answer": "BARNARD",
    "Correct": 0
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 262,
    "Question": "WHAT IS THE LAST NAME OF THE MAN WHO SAID “I ONLY REGRET THAT I HAVE BUT ONE LIFE TO LOSE FOR MY COUNTRY”?",
    "Answer": "HALE",
    "Correct": 0
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 263,
    "Question": "WHAT IS THE LAST NAME OF THE PILOT OF THE U-2 SPY PLANE SHOT DOWN OVER RUSSIA IN 1960?",
    "Answer": "POWERS",
    "Correct": 0
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 264,
    "Question": "WHAT IS THE LAST NAME OF THE ACTOR WHO PORTRAYED THE SHERIFF IN THE MOVIE “HIGH NOON”?",
    "Answer": "COOPER",
    "Correct": 0
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 265,
    "Question": "WHAT IS THE NAME OF THE MOUNTAIN RANGE THAT SEPARATES ASIA FROM EUROPE?",
    "Answer": "URAL",
    "Correct": 0
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 266,
    "Question": "WHAT IS THE LAST NAME OF THE BOXER WHO WAS KNOWN AS THE “MANASSA MAULER”?",
    "Answer": "DEMPSEY",
    "Correct": 0
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 267,
    "Question": "WHAT IS THE LAST NAME OF THE MAN WHO CREATED THE COMIC STRIP “LI’L ABNER”?",
    "Answer": "CAPP",
    "Correct": 0
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 268,
    "Question": "WHAT IS THE LAST NAME OF THE BASEBALL PLAYER WHO PITCHED A PERFECT GAME IN THE 1956 WORLD SERIES?",
    "Answer": "LARSEN",
    "Correct": 0
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 269,
    "Question": "WHAT IS THE LAST NAME OF THE FIRST MAN TO RUN THE MILE IN UNDER FOUR MINUTES?",
    "Answer": "BANNISTER",
    "Correct": 0
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 270,
    "Question": "WHAT IS THE LAST NAME OF THE AUTHOR WHO WROTE “BROTHERS KARAMAZOV”?",
    "Answer": "DOSTOYEVSKI",
    "Correct": 0
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 271,
    "Question": "WHAT IS THE NAME OF THE AUTHOR WHO RECEIVED A PULITZER PRIZE FOR HIS WRITINGS ABOUT ABRAHAM LINCOLN?",
    "Answer": "SANDBURG",
    "Correct": 0
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 272,
    "Question": "WHAT IS THE LAST NAME OF THE MAN WHO CREATED THE COMIC STRIP “WOODY WOODPECKER”?",
    "Answer": "LANTZ",
    "Correct": 0
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 273,
    "Question": "WHAT IS THE NAME OF THE INSTRUMENT USED TO MEASURE WIND SPEED?",
    "Answer": "ANEMOMETER",
    "Correct": 0
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 274,
    "Question": "WHAT IS THE LAST NAME OF THE AUTHOR OF “OUR TOWN”?",
    "Answer": "WILDER",
    "Correct": 0
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 275,
    "Question": "WHAT IS THE LAST NAME OF THE SINGER WHO MADE A HIT RECORDING OF THE SONG “WHO’S SORRY NOW”?",
    "Answer": "FRANCIS",
    "Correct": 0
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 276,
    "Question": "WHAT IS THE LAST NAME OF THE CUBAN LEADER THAT CASTRO OVERTHREW?",
    "Answer": "BATISTA",
    "Correct": 0
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 277,
    "Question": "WHAT IS THE NAME OF THE RUBBER ROLLER ON A TYPEWRITER?",
    "Answer": "PLATEN",
    "Correct": 0
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 278,
    "Question": "WHAT WAS THE NAME OF THE LARGEST CONFEDERATE MILITARY PRISON DURING THE CIVIL WAR?",
    "Answer": "ANDERSONVILLE",
    "Correct": 0
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 279,
    "Question": "WHAT IS THE LAST NAME OF THE AUTHOR OF “THE AGONY AND THE ECSTASY”?",
    "Answer": "STONE",
    "Correct": 0
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 280,
    "Question": "WHAT IS THE LAST NAME OF FLASH’S GIRLFRIEND IN THE COMIC STRIP “FLASH GORDON”?",
    "Answer": "ARDEN",
    "Correct": 0
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 281,
    "Question": "WHAT IS THE NAME OF THE FIRST MOVIE TO RECEIVE THE ACADEMY AWARD FOR BEST PICTURE?",
    "Answer": "WINGS",
    "Correct": 0
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 282,
    "Question": "WHAT IS THE LAST NAME OF THE DISCOVERER OF THE VACCINATION FOR SMALLPOX?",
    "Answer": "JENNER",
    "Correct": 0
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 283,
    "Question": "WHAT IS THE LAST NAME OF THE BOY IN THE BOOK “TREASURE ISLAND”?",
    "Answer": "HAWKINS",
    "Correct": 0
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 284,
    "Question": "WHAT IS THE LAST NAME OF THE BOXER WHO WON THE BOXING TITLE FROM JOHN L. SULLIVAN?",
    "Answer": "CORBETT",
    "Correct": 0
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 285,
    "Question": "WHAT IS THE LAST NAME OF THE MAN WHO WROTE THE SONG “HOW DEEP IS THE OCEAN”?",
    "Answer": "BERLIN",
    "Correct": 0
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 286,
    "Question": "WHAT WAS THE LAST NAME OF BILLY THE KID?",
    "Answer": "BONNEY",
    "Correct": 0
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 287,
    "Question": "WHAT IS THE LAST NAME OF THE SINGER WHOSE THEME SONG WAS “WHEN THE BLUE OF THE NIGHT MEETS THE GOLD OF THE DAY”?",
    "Answer": "CROSBY",
    "Correct": 0
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 288,
    "Question": "FROM WHAT MUSICAL IS THE SONG “BAUBLES BANGLES AND BEADS”?",
    "Answer": "KISMET",
    "Correct": 0
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 289,
    "Question": "WHAT WAS THE LAST NAME OF THE ACTOR WHO PORTRAYED DR. WATSON IN THE SHERLOCK HOLMES SERIES?",
    "Answer": "BRUCE",
    "Correct": 0
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 290,
    "Question": "WHAT IS THE LAST NAME OF THE MAN WHO WAS MOST RESPONSIBLE FOR PHOTOGRAPHING THE U.S. CIVIL WAR?",
    "Answer": "BRADY",
    "Correct": 0
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 291,
    "Question": "WHAT IS THE NAME OF A NUMBER TWO WOOD IN GOLF?",
    "Answer": "BRASSIE",
    "Correct": 0
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 292,
    "Question": "WHAT IS THE LAST NAME OF THE POET WHO WROTE THE LINE “INTO EACH LIFE A LITTLE RAIN MUST FALL”?",
    "Answer": "LONGFELLOW",
    "Correct": 0
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 293,
    "Question": "WHAT WAS THE NAME OF GENE AUTRY’S HORSE?",
    "Answer": "CHAMPION",
    "Correct": 0
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 294,
    "Question": "WHAT IS THE NAME OF THE TOWN THROUGH WHICH LADY GODIVA SUPPOSEDLY MADE HER FAMOUS RIDE?",
    "Answer": "COVENTRY",
    "Correct": 0
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 295,
    "Question": "WHAT IS THE LAST NAME OF THE FIRST WOMAN TO SWIM ACROSS THE ENGLISH CHANNEL?",
    "Answer": "EDERLE",
    "Correct": 0
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 296,
    "Question": "WHAT IS THE LAST NAME OF THE FIRST FLIER TO FLY SOLO AROUND THE WORLD?",
    "Answer": "POST",
    "Correct": 0
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 297,
    "Question": "WHAT IS THE LAST NAME OF THE MAN WHO WROTE THE POEM “IT COULDN’T BE DONE”?",
    "Answer": "GUEST",
    "Correct": 0
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 298,
    "Question": "WHO WAS THE RACEHORSE OF THE YEAR FOR MANY SUCCESSIVE YEARS IN THE 1960S?",
    "Answer": "KELSO",
    "Correct": 0
  },
  {
    "2012 Rank": 299,
    "Question": "WHAT IS THE HIGHEST MOUNTAIN IN SOUTH AMERICA?",
    "Answer": "ACONCAGUA",
    "Correct": 0
  }
]